# Jen Sandage

Forest Grove, OR 97116

(620) 719-7026 • jensandage1@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-sandage-469899130/

#### **SUMMARY**

Web developer with a background in education. Trained through University of Oregon Full Stack Bootcamp. Creative problem-solver with experience communicating and developing rubrics. Experienced in projects from big ideas and breaking it down into smaller measurable steps based on research.

#### **EDUCATION:**

est. Oct 2023 **Certificate of Completion** - University of Oregon, Eugene, OR Full Stack Developer Coding Bootcamp

2015-2016 **Master of Arts in Teaching** (MAT) – Concordia University, Portland, OR Preliminary Teaching License – Pre-K – 12: ART

2010-2014 **Bachelor of Science in Psychology –** Pittsburg State University, Pittsburg, KS Emphasis in Developmental Disabilities

## **WORK HISTORY:**

## 08/2022-06/2023 - Substitute Teacher

SOESD, Medford, OR

Implement materials left by classroom teacher Maintain classroom management

#### 08/2018-06/2022 - Art Teacher K-12

Roque River School District, Rogue River, OR

Plan and implement lesson plans based on state standards
Maintain classroom management with classes up to thirty students
Communicate with staff, students, and parents
Create collaborative lessons with other arts teachers

## 06/2017-04/2018 - Pre-kindergarten Teacher

Knowledge Beginnings, Tigard, OR

Plan and implement lesson plans based on curriculum Maintain classroom management Communicate with families

#### 08/2016-06/2017 - Substitute Teacher

CTE Substitute Services, Hillsboro, OR

Implement materials left by classroom teacher Maintain classroom management

# **Skills:**

Group Management Curriculum Development

Communication Creativity
HTML CSS
Javascript SQL
APIs React